<Publish>
  <ModId Value="74238" />
  <DisplayName Value="Extended Transport Manager" />
  <ShortDescription Value="Expanded tools for public transport management." />
  <LongDescription># Extended Transport Manager
## _A better view of public transport_

This is successor from both Transport Lines Manager (TLM) and Improved Transport Manager (ITM) from CS1. 

The overall idea is bring some tools to better manage and visualize the public transport of the city.

## Current features

- Auto color - import palettes to the city then apply to transport type
  - 20+ default palletes included.
  - Create your own palettes using the game UI
  - Palettes can be grouped in "folders" to organize better your library
  - Palettes used in the city are now saved along them. No more issues if changing the global palettes!
- Line listing - Very simple by now, might be improved in the future
- Detailed linear map - View detailed info about stops, vehicles and also transport integrations
- Customize line naming - You can use the game name pattern to use the route identifier as you wish, using any kind of characters
- Lines shields - like it was in TLM:
  - Hexagon for buses
  - Trapeze for trams
  - Square for metro
  - Circle for passenger trains
  - Diamond for passenger ships
  - Pentagon for passenger airplanes
  - Octogon for freight trains (NEW)
  - 8-point star for freight ships (NEW)
  - Thick square cross for freight airplanes (NEW)

## Experimental mod warning!
Since it's a very complex mod, it may cause issues in the game due their early stage of development. This mod may take months until get the same number of features it had in CS1.

## Support

The most up to date information about installation and known issues and bugs are in the forums topic.)</LongDescription>
  <Thumbnail Value="Properties/Thumbnail.png" />
  <ForumLink Value="https://forum.paradoxplaza.com/forum/threads/xtm-extended-transport-manager.1651555/" />
  <ModVersion Value="0.1.2.2" />
  <GameVersion Value="1.1.*" />
  <ChangeLog># v0.1.3r0 (??-JUN-24)
- Economy 2.0 update
- Fixed error when clicking on a line with no vehicles - _TypeError: Cannot read properties of undefined (reading '1')_)</ChangeLog>
  <Tag Value="Code Mod" />
  <Screenshot Value="Screenshots\00_lineListing.jpg" />
  <Screenshot Value="Screenshots\01_LineData.jpg" />
  <Screenshot Value="Screenshots\02_mapview.jpg" />
  <Screenshot Value="Screenshots\03_MapOptions.jpg" />
  <Screenshot Value="Screenshots\04_palletes.jpg" />
  <Dependency Id="74151" ModVersion="0.1.1.2" DisplayName="Extra UI Screens" />
</Publish>