<Publish>
  <ModId Value="74238" />
  <DisplayName Value="Extended Transport Manager" />
  <ShortDescription Value="Expanded tools for public transport management." />
  <LongDescription># Extended Transport Manager
## _A better view of public transport_

This is successor from both Transport Lines Manager (TLM) and Improved Transport Manager (ITM) from CS1. 

The overall idea is bring some tools to better manage and visualize the public transport of the city.

## How to find the mod screen

If using single monitor, use the [EUIS](https://mods.paradoxplaza.com/mods/74151/Windows) mod shortcut to open the main screen overlay over the game screen, then find this mod icon in the taskbar. By default, it's `Ctrl+Tab`.

When using multiple monitors, it may be visible in any of them, except if disabled at EUIS settings screen.

## Current features

- Auto color - import palettes to the city then apply to transport type
  - 20+ default palletes included.
  - Create your own palettes using the game UI
  - Palettes can be grouped in "folders" to organize better your library
  - Palettes used in the city are now saved along them. No more issues if changing the global palettes!
- Line listing - Very simple by now, might be improved in the future
- Detailed linear map - View detailed info about stops, vehicles and also transport integrations
- Customize line naming - You can use the game name pattern to use the route identifier as you wish, using any kind of characters
- Lines shields - like it was in TLM:
  - Hexagon for buses
  - Trapeze for trams
  - Square for metro
  - Circle for passenger trains
  - Diamond for passenger ships
  - Pentagon for passenger airplanes
  - Octogon for freight trains (NEW)
  - 8-point star for freight ships (NEW)
  - Thick square cross for freight airplanes (NEW)

**Note:** Check full features by reading the changelogs. The features above are just the initial feature set. 
	

## Experimental mod warning!
Since it's a very complex mod, it may cause issues in the game due their early stage of development. This mod may take months until get the same number of features it had in CS1.

## Support

The most up to date information about installation and known issues and bugs are in the forums topic.</LongDescription>
  <Thumbnail Value="Properties/Thumbnail.png" />
  <ForumLink Value="https://forum.paradoxplaza.com/forum/threads/xtm-extended-transport-manager.1651555/" />
  <ModVersion Value="0.1.3.0" />
  <GameVersion Value="1.1.*" />
  <ChangeLog># v0.1.3r0 (24-JUN-24)
- Economy 2.0 update
- New side tabs to navigate between mod screens
- Added requirement to subscribe the Unified Icon Library
- Initial implementation of stop details screen when clicking in a stop of the map:
	- Added button to define a stop as first stop of a line)
	- Also added buttons for: focus to stop, select stop and select building of the stop (if applicable)
- Added simetric view mode on line viewers for lines that are detected as simetric (like generally rail lines are)
  - NOTE: it detects based on stop buildings ownership, so custom station buildings stops (that not belongs to an asset) may not be detetected...
- Added support to exporting palettes from city to a .hex file under `&lt;Palettes Folder&gt;/Exported` folder. You can share the file with other players.
- Added support to subfolders under the palettes folder. Each subfolder will have a folded group in the palette library screen.
- Added buttons to go to palette folder in some palette related screens.
- Added button to reload palettes from folder at palette library screen.
- Fixed error when clicking on a line with no vehicles - _TypeError: Cannot read properties of undefined (reading '1')_</ChangeLog>
  <Tag Value="Code Mod" />
  <Screenshot Value="Screenshots\00_lineListing.jpg" />
  <Screenshot Value="Screenshots\01_LineData.jpg" />
  <Screenshot Value="Screenshots\02_mapview.jpg" />
  <Screenshot Value="Screenshots\03_MapOptions.jpg" />
  <Screenshot Value="Screenshots\04_palletes.jpg" />
  <Dependency Id="74151" ModVersion="" DisplayName="Extra UI Screens" />
  <Dependency Id="74417" ModVersion="" DisplayName="Unified Icon Library" />
</Publish>